[EPIC]⚡ These cops and lawyers wouldn't dare cross any of you.
[EPIC]⚡ I mean, what happened?
[EPIC]⚡ So what are you proposing?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 It's simple.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Kill the Batman.
[EPIC]⚡ Here's my card.
[EPIC]⚡ Bruce, it's Harvey Dent.
[EPIC]⚡ Rachel's told me everything about you.
[EPIC]⚡ I certainly hope not.
[EPIC]⚡ You almost told me that we'd be together.
[EPIC]⚡ Did you mean it?
[EPIC]⚡ Bruce, don't make me your only hope for a normal life.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You're Alfred, right?
[EPIC]⚡ That's right, son.
[EPIC]⚡ Any psychotic ex -boyfriends I should be aware of?
[EPIC]⚡ Oh, you have no idea.
[EPIC]⚡ Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
[EPIC]⚡ We're tonight's entertainment.
[EPIC]⚡ Well, hello, beautiful.
[EPIC]⚡ You look nervous.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You now would have to become to stop men like him.
[EPIC]⚡ The night is darkest just before the dawn.
[EPIC]⚡ And I promise you, the dawn is coming.
[EPIC]⚡ And here we...
[EPIC]⚡ This city deserves a better class of criminal.
[EPIC]⚡ I'm gonna give it to him.
[EPIC]⚡ No!
[EPIC]⚡ You'll see.
[EPIC]⚡ I'll show you.
[EPIC]⚡ You either die a hero
[EPIC]⚡ or you live long enough to see yourself become the villain.
[EPIC]⚡ Be one in the back putt, sir.
[EPIC]⚡ In the middle of the day, Alfred, not very subtle.
[EPIC]⚡ Much more subtle.